{
"translations": {
    "en": {
    "q0": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What can you change the $\\lambda$ connection to?",
        "description": "The DFA does not accept $\\lambda$ expression",
        "answer": "b",
        "choices": ["a", "b", "c"]
    },
    "q1": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q3, q4\\}$ with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state:",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
        "answer": "q1, q5, q6",
        "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"q4"]
    },
    "q2": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is transition from state $\\{q1, q5, q6\\}$ with the alphabet a. Select the appropriate state:",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
        "answer": "q3",
        "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q3, q4, q5" ,"q3"]
    },
    "q3": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q1, q5, q6\\}$ with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state:",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
        "answer": "No Transition",
        "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"No Transition"]
    },
    "q4": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q3\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
        "answer": "No Transition",
        "choices": ["q4", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5" ,"No Transition"]
    },
    "q5": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the trnsition from state $\\{q3\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
        "answer": "q5, q1",
        "choices": ["q6","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
    },
    "q6": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q4\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
        "answer": "q6",
        "choices": ["q6", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No Transition"]
    },
    "q7": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the trnsition from state $\\{q4\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to",
        "answer": "No transition",
        "choices": ["q6","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
    },
    "q8": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q5, q1\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
        "answer": "q3",
        "choices": ["q3", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No transition"]
    },
    "q9": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the trnsition from state $\\{q5, q1\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
        "answer": "No transition",
        "choices": ["q3","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
    },
    "q10": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q6\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
        "answer": "No transition",
        "choices": ["q6", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No transition"]
    },
    "q11": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q6\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
        "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
        "answer": "No transition",
        "choices": ["q3","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
    },
    "q12notUSed": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "src": "../../../AV/FLA/billyu/ui/FAFixer.html",
        "question":"What is the final state?",
        "answer": "q1, q2, q3",
        "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q5, q6","q4" ]
    },
    "q13": {
        "type": "select",
        "question":"What are the final state? Note that, any state that include states $q5$ or $q6$ should be a final state",
        "answer": ["q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6", "q6"],
        "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q3, q4","q4", "q1, q5, q6", "q3", "q6", "q5, q1"]
    }
    }
}
}
  